Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers
1998 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
African Union High-Level Implementation Panel for Sudan
Erasmus, Neha
MS207
1953 Digital Object(s)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are noted in the Detailed Contents List in each series.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Subject files; and Negotiations records.
Biographical / Historical
Neha Erasmus grew up in Kenya. She worked in Southern Sudan with the Institute for the Promotion of Civil Society. She is a Justice Africa board member and a Political Officer of the African Union High-Level Implementation Panel on Sudan. Her primary role as a political officer was to provide administrative support to the other members of the panel. She worked consistently on security issues and occasionally on oil issues. Erasmus worked closely with Chief of Staff, Abdul Mohammed.
Custodial History
This collection was transferred from Neha on a thumb drive to the World Peace Foundation. The DCA copied the files from the World Peace Foundation's network drive to our facilities for archival management.
In October/November 2011 Neha's filing process changed. Originally she had filed her documents topically by subject. However, as the negotiations progressed and became more complicated, she found it necessary to file most of the work by month. This change in strategy is represented by the two distinct series.
This collection was part of a series of collections the World Peace Foundation collected as part of their grant "Documentation, Research and Writing on the African Union High Level Implementation Panel for Sudan" funded by the United States Institute of Peace.
Related Materials
MS201. Alex de Waal African Union High-Level Implementation Panel papers. DCA.
MS205. Dave Mozersky African Union High-Level Implementation Panel papers. DCA.
MS206. Laura James African Union High-Level Implementation Panel papers. DCA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the subject files, meeting minutes and agendas, correspondence, a few photographs of negotiation efforts, negotiation strategy documents, and topical reports relating to Neha Erasmus's work as part of the African Union High-Level Implementation panel on Sudan (AUHIP) primarily between 2010 and 2013. As the primary coordinator and secretariat of the panel, Neha coordinated the efforts of the other members of the panel. Her collection contains many of the final summary documents as well as the administrative documents necessary to coordinate the AUHIP's efforts. The collection does not have many financial or budgetary documents.
Foreign affairs; Social justice; Social justice
- Subject files, 1998 -- 2013; MS207.001; 1042 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the topical subject files, meeting minutes and agendas, correspondence, strategy documents, and reports relating to Neha Erasmus's work as part of the African Union High-Level Implementation panel on Sudan (AUHIP) primarily between 2010 and 2011. Topics include the Abyei negotiations, borders, economics, framework documents, implementation efforts, Joint Technical Secretariat committees, the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, and negotiation strategies. Beginning around October or November in 2011, Neha ceased filing everything by topic and instead organized everything chronologically by month. Topical overlap occurs with series 2.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject file and chronologically within subject.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Abyei, 2001 -- 2012; MS207.001.00001
    Open for research.
    - Abyei Joint Oversight Committee, 2011; MS207.001.00002
      - Background Information: Implementation of the Temporary Abyei Agreement, 2011-08-05; MS207.001.00003
        75 years from the date of creation.
      - Agenda AJOC / Abyei Implementation Meeting, 2011-09-06; MS207.001.00004
      - Draft AJOC Agenda, 2011-08-26; MS207.001.00005
    - Draft report on Abyei, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00006
      - A letter from President Kiir to Mbeki, 2012-09-25; MS207.001.00007
      - GoS response to AUHIP, 2012-09-23 -- 2012-09-25; MS207.001.00008
      - Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Government of the Republic of South Sudan On the Resolution of the Final Status of Abyei, 2012-09-26; MS207.001.00009
      - Proposal on the Final Status of the Abyei Area., 2012-09-21; MS207.001.00010
      - Report to the AU PSC on the Outstanding Matter of the Resolution of the Final Status of Abyei, 2012-10-07; MS207.001.00011
      - AUHIP Proposal Towards a Resolution of the Issue of Abyei, 2010-11-27; MS207.001.00012
    - Letters, 2011; MS207.001.00013
      - AUHIP letter AJOC GoRSS, 2011-12-04; MS207.001.00014
      - AUHIP letter AJOC GoRSS, 2011-12-04; MS207.001.00015
      - AUHIP letter AJOC GoS, 2011-12-04; MS207.001.00016
      - AUHIP letter AJOC GoS, 2011-12-04; MS207.001.00017
      - AUHIP letter OB, 2011-12-02; MS207.001.00018
      - AUHIP letter SK, 2011-12-02; MS207.001.00019
    - Transboundary Protected Area, 2001 -- 2010; MS207.001.00020
      - Introduction: A Natural Connection between Ecology and Peace?, 2007; MS207.001.00021
      - Transboundary Protected Areas as a Vehicle for Peaceful Co-Operation, 2010-11-12; MS207.001.00022
      - Creating a Transboundary Protected Area in Abyei, 2010-11-14; MS207.001.00023
      - Transboundary Protected Areas for Peace and Co-operation, 2001; MS207.001.00024
    - Abyei Roadmap Agreement, 2008-06-08; MS207.001.00025
    - Update on U.S.-Brokered Negotiations in Abyei, 3-7 October 2010, 2010-10-07; MS207.001.00026
    - Options Brainstorming Table for Abyei "Out of the Box", 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00027
    - Meeting Brainstorming Abyei 271010, 2010-10-27; MS207.001.00028
    - Action Points Abyei Security, 2011-01-21; MS207.001.00029
    - Text for Announcement on Abyei Security, 2011-03-18; MS207.001.00030
    - A.U. Panel Proposal for the Resolution of the Status of Abyei Area, 2011-03-19; MS207.001.00031
    - The Engagement of the AU Panel on Abyei, 2011-05-08; MS207.001.00032
    - Interim Security Force for Abyei, 2011-05-22; MS207.001.00033
    - Interim Security Arrangements for Abyei, 2011-05-28; MS207.001.00034
    - SAF CPA Security Arrangements v2, 2011-05-29; MS207.001.00035
    - Draft Proposal, 2011-06-02; MS207.001.00036
    - Meeting with on Abyei: 31 August 2011, 2011-08-31; MS207.001.00037
    - African Union High-Level Implementation Panel Proposal for the Resolution of the Status of Abyei Area, 2011-09-11; MS207.001.00038
    - AUHIP Proposed Schedule for Meetings of Abyei Administrative Bodies and Redeployment Process of Unauthorised Forces, 2011-11-16; MS207.001.00039
    - memo AUHIP TFA plane request, 2011-11-17; MS207.001.00040
  - Borders, 1998 -- 2013; MS207.001.00041
    - African Union technical work on Borders, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.001.00042
      - Ilemi triangle map, 2013-05-06; MS207.001.00043
      - Map Abyei: A Comparative Map, 2013-05-06; MS207.001.00044
      - Map, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00045
    - Governor's meeting, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00046
      - Governor's Budget, 2010-02-05; MS207.001.00047
      - Governor's Meeting 19 - 20 Feb, 2011-01-30; MS207.001.00048
      - Concept Note for Convening the Border Governors, 2011-01-31; MS207.001.00049
      - Talking Points for Meetings with the Governors, 2011-01-31; MS207.001.00050
      - Sudan Border Govs meeting Invite AUBP, 2011-02-06; MS207.001.00051
      - Sudan Border Govs meeting Draft Invite AUBP, 2011-02-06; MS207.001.00052
      - Sudan Border Govs meeting Draft Invite AUBP, 2011-02-06; MS207.001.00053
      - Sudan Border Govs meeting Draft Invite AUBP AUSD, 2011-02-06; MS207.001.00054
      - Talking Points for Meetings with the Governors, 2011-02-06; MS207.001.00055
      - Draft Agenda for the Border Governor's Meeting, 2011-02-07; MS207.001.00056
      - AUHIP Invite Governors, 2011-02-08; MS207.001.00057
      - Draft Agenda for the Border Governor's Meeting, 2011-02-08; MS207.001.00058
      - Guideline Questions for Thinking on the Proposal, 2011-02-08; MS207.001.00059
      - Postponement of the Governors Consultation 19-20 Feb 2011, Damazin, Sudan, 2011-02-17; MS207.001.00060
      - AUHIP Letter VPs Border Meeting, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00061
      - AUHIP Border Conference Invitation, 2011-04-20; MS207.001.00062
    - Soft border, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00063
      - Proposed Program, 2010-10-13; MS207.001.00064
      - Soft border - Grazing Rights, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00065
      - Soft Border - Regulatory Framework and Institutions on Migration, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00066
      - Soft Border - Security around Migration, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00067
      - Soft Border Migration related Infrastructure and Services, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00068
      - Framework for Promoting a future Soft Border between North and South Sudan, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00069
      - Talking Points for Meetings with the Governors, 2011-02-03; MS207.001.00070
    - SPLM Boundary report, 2011; MS207.001.00071
      - Anim presentation, 2011-03-30; MS207.001.00072
      - The Boundary Technical Demarcation Committee between North Sudan and its Southern Part 1/1/1956, 2011-03-30; MS207.001.00073
      - presentation on borders, 2011-03-29; MS207.001.00074
      - The Boundary Technical Demarcation Committee Between North Sudan, 2011-03-30; MS207.001.00075
    - Tamazaj, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00076
      - Ten States Conference Briefing, 2010-02-02; MS207.001.00077
      - The second conference of Tamasuj (intermingling States North Bahr Al Ghazal States, 2010-07-19; MS207.001.00078
      - Matrix of the Recommendations of the First and Second Symposiums of the Intermixture States, 2011-01-26; MS207.001.00079
      - first reflections forum for Tamazuj states towards peace, tamazuj and development, 2011-02-10; MS207.001.00080
      - The First Consultative Meeting for the bordering states, 2010-02-27 -- 2010-02-28; MS207.001.00081
    - UK Symposium, 2011; MS207.001.00082
      - High-level symposium on border management and security, 2011-01-25; MS207.001.00083
      - Comments on the UK Symposium on Soft Borders, 2011-01-26; MS207.001.00084
    - Ecowas Transhumance Agreement, 1998-10; MS207.001.00085
    - Sudan and South Sudan Border disputes and conflicts, 2010-05-06; MS207.001.00086
    - A Soft but Secure Border - Framework Border Language, 2010-12-09; MS207.001.00087
    - Grazing Rights and Mechanisms to regulate transhumance of Pastoral Nomads Across North-South Sudan Borders, 2010-12-11; MS207.001.00088
    - Agreement on Cross Border Issues, 2010-12-28; MS207.001.00089
    - Resolution of the disputed areas of the North South border - final update-3, 2011-01-26; MS207.001.00090
    - Postponement of the Governors Consultation 19-20 Feb 2011, Damazin, Sudan, 2011-02-17; MS207.001.00091
    - The Centreline of the Safe Demilitarized Border Zone Portraying 10 KM Buffer Zones, 2013-02-25; MS207.001.00092
    - Border map, 2013-02-25; MS207.001.00093
    - Border map, 2013-05-06; MS207.001.00094
  - Citizenship, 2011; MS207.001.00095
    - Agreement Between the Government of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement on Citizenship and Related Matters, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00096
  - Civil Society, 2010; MS207.001.00097
    - The National Organization to Support Voluntary Unity Over all vision of the relationship between the North and the South, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00098
  - Communications, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.001.00099
    - AUHIP Briefing, 2010-09-07; MS207.001.00100
    - AU Ambassador to the Sudan, 2010-09-13; MS207.001.00101
    - Media Contacts List, 2010-09-22; MS207.001.00102
    - AUHIP Press Release Code of Conduct, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00103
    - The African Union Welcomes the Start of Direct Negotiations on the Conflict in the Two Areas, 2013-04-06; MS207.001.00104
    - Direct talks in Addis Ababa between the Government of Sudan and the SPLM-North, 2013-04-26; MS207.001.00105
  - Confidential, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00106
    - Secretary-General's Panel Terms of Reference, 2010-08-17; MS207.001.00107
    - Non-Paper on How to Conclude a Political/Peace Agreement for Darfur, 2010-09; MS207.001.00108
    - A letter from Mbeki to Gazi, 2010-09-05; MS207.001.00109
    - Memo - Dear Professor Gambari - 050910, 2010-09-05; MS207.001.00110
    - Abdul Mohammed and Alex de Waal letter to Mbeki about Ghazi, 2010-09-07; MS207.001.00111
    - Update and Next Steps, 2011-05-10; MS207.001.00112
    - Mediation Strategy, 2011-05-14; MS207.001.00113
    - AUHIP letter Jean Ping, 2011-08-02; MS207.001.00114
    - Alliance of the Sudanese Revolutionary Front Political Declaration, 2011-08-07; MS207.001.00115
    - Meeting between PM Meles Zenawi and SPLMN Chairman Malik Agar Eyre, 2011-08-10; MS207.001.00116
  - Darfur, 2006 -- 2011; MS207.001.00117
    - Darfur Peace Agreement, 2006; MS207.001.00118
    - Meeting Sudan Government Security Strategy, 2010-08-26; MS207.001.00119; De Waal, Alexander
    - AU informal report on Doha, 2010-09-01; MS207.001.00120
    - Senior Management Retreat for the UN Integrated Strategic Framework (ISF) for Darfur, 2010-09-01; MS207.001.00121
    - Note to Mbeki-new Darfur strategy, 2010-09-01; MS207.001.00122
    - Letter to Mbeki from Abdul Mohammed and Alex de Waal, 2010-09-07; MS207.001.00123
    - Concept Note and Outline Plan Darfur-Darfur Conference, 2010-10-13; MS207.001.00124
    - Meeting Ghazi Alex Effendi, 2010-10-14; MS207.001.00125
    - Sudan, 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00126
    - Memorandum on Darfur Political Process, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00127
    - Agenda 1, 2010-11-13; MS207.001.00128
    - Meeting with DDDC, 2010-11-13; MS207.001.00129
    - African Union Commissioner for Peace and Security Code Cable, 2010-11-26; MS207.001.00130
    - Creating an Enabling Environment for a Darfur-Based Political Process, 2010-12-15; MS207.001.00131
    - Darfur -Darfur Dialoge and Consultation program strategy and work plan, 2011-01 -- 2011-12; MS207.001.00132
    - DDDC wkplan, 2011-01 -- 2011-12; MS207.001.00133
    - Plan for Supporting the Closure of Doha and Commencement of the Darfur Political Process (DPP), 2011-01-06; MS207.001.00134
    - African Union Commissioner for Peace and Security Code Cable, 2011-01-12; MS207.001.00135
    - Observations, 2011-01-13; MS207.001.00136
    - Meeting on Darfur, 2011-01-15; MS207.001.00137
    - Plan of Action Darfur Political Process/All Darfur Conference, 2011-01-16; MS207.001.00138
    - Plan of Action Darfur Political Process/All Darfur Conference, 2011-01-16; MS207.001.00139
    - Darfur Timeline, 2011-01-16; MS207.001.00140
    - Societal Security in Darfur Concept Note, 2011-01-20; MS207.001.00141
    - Social Peace Security Comments, 2011-01-21; MS207.001.00142
    - Darfur Dialogue outcome document, 2011-01-26; MS207.001.00143
    - Response to Bassole from Ghazi, 2011-02-02; MS207.001.00144
    - Darfur Implementation Plan, 2011-02-03; MS207.001.00145
    - Letter from Abdul Mohamed - Request for Extension of Consultancy contract of Mr Abdi Yunis, 2011-03-17; MS207.001.00146
    - Letter from Abdul Mohamed - Request for Extension of Consultancy contract of Mr Abdi Yunis, 2011-03-17; MS207.001.00147
    - Draft Code Cable, 2011-03-30; MS207.001.00148
    - Concluding a Political Agreement for Darfur, 2011-05-01; MS207.001.00149
    - Four Way Meeting on Darfur, 2011-05-09; MS207.001.00150
    - Terms of Reference, 2011-05-22; MS207.001.00151
    - AU-UN Workshop on The Way Forward for Darfur, 2011-08-18; MS207.001.00152
    - Economics Checklist, 2011-10-05; MS207.001.00153
  - Democratisation, 2011 -- 2012; MS207.001.00154
    - Democratization and the constitutional process, 2011-10-22; MS207.001.00155
    - Achieving a Democratic Transition in Sudan?, 2012-01-08; MS207.001.00156
    - Democratization in the Republic of Sudan, 2012-01-16; MS207.001.00157
    - The Prospects for Political Reform in Sudan:, 2012-01-18; MS207.001.00158
  - Economics, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00159
    - Economics Cluster meeting, 2010; MS207.001.00160
      - Meeting Economics Cluster: Juba 221210, 2010-12-22; MS207.001.00161
      - Summary of Economics Cluster Meeting, Juba 221210, 2010-12-22; MS207.001.00162
    - Kuriftu III, 2011; MS207.001.00163
      - Options papers and agendas, 2011; MS207.001.00164
        - Meeting of the Economic "Super-group", 2011-05-16; MS207.001.00165
        - Options Paper on the Handling of Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South, 2011-05-17; MS207.001.00166
        - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster - AUHIP Debt Options Paper, 2011-05-17; MS207.001.00167
        - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub-group, 2011-05-16; MS207.001.00168
        - Matrix of Preparations on Economic Issues, 2011-04-17; MS207.001.00169
        - Super Group Invitation, 2011-04-20; MS207.001.00170
        - Economic negotiation 19 - 21 May, Debre Zeyit, Ethiopia, 2011-05-18; MS207.001.00171
        - Room Allocation Economics Negotiations, 2011-05-18; MS207.001.00172
    - Water, 2011; MS207.001.00173
      - Second Round of Finance, Economic and Natural Resources Cluster Negotiations, 2011-04-09; MS207.001.00174
    - AU meeting with Economic affairs cluster, 2010-12-19; MS207.001.00175
    - Post referendum arrangments' negotiations economic, finance and natural resources working group, 2010-12-22; MS207.001.00176
    - Attendance List for Economics Negotiations, 2011-02-05; MS207.001.00177
    - Economic Negotiations at Kuriftu Resort and Spa,Bishoftu, Ethiopia, 2011-04-08; MS207.001.00178
    - Background to the Sudan/South Sudan Economic Negotiations, 2011-04-08; MS207.001.00179
    - Draft Text for Note Verbale Requesting Meetings with Creditors, 2011-04-10; MS207.001.00180
    - Note Verbale to UK, 2011-04-10; MS207.001.00181
    - LNP Meeting, 2011-04-11; MS207.001.00182
    - Proposed schedule of economic cluster meetings - April/May 2011, 2011-05-01; MS207.001.00183
    - The Facilitator's Memorandum to the Parties, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00184
    - The Facilitator's Memorandum to the Parties, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00185
    - Resuming the Economic Negotiations - draft, 2011-08-01; MS207.001.00186
    - Post-Secession Arrangements Negotiations Joint Technical Secretariat Khartoum, 2011-08-08; MS207.001.00187
    - Planning matrix for September economic negotiations, 2011-08-10; MS207.001.00188
  - Elections, Political parties meetings, 2007 -- 2010; MS207.001.00189
    - Model Code of Conduct for the Guidance of Political Parties and Candidates, 2007; MS207.001.00190
    - AUHIP Letter head, 2010-02-15; MS207.001.00191
    - Agenda for Summit Meeting of Political Parties, 2010-02-15; MS207.001.00192
    - Electoral Code of Conduct for Sudan March 2010, 2010-02-15; MS207.001.00193
    - AUHIP Meeting with Opposition Parties, 2010-02-17; MS207.001.00194
    - Election Observer Complaints Mechanism, 2010-02-17; MS207.001.00195
    - Staff Contact details, 2010-02-18; MS207.001.00196
    - Arrivals Times and Details for Participants, 2010-02-28; MS207.001.00197
    - South Sudan Political Parties Contact List, 2010-02-28; MS207.001.00198
    - South Sudan Political Parties Contact List, 2010-02-28; MS207.001.00199
    - South Sudan Political Parties Contact List, 2010-03-01; MS207.001.00200
    - South Sudan Political Parties Registration List, 2010-03-01; MS207.001.00201
    - Funds transfer request form, 2010-03-01; MS207.001.00202
    - Abdul Memo, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00203
    - Declaration Common Commitment Final, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00204
    - Joint Statement - draft, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00205
    - South Sudan Political Parties Registration List, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00206
    - Electoral Code of Conduct for Sudan March 2010, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00207
    - Electoral Code of Conduct for Sudan March 2010, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00208
    - Electoral Code of Conduct for Sudan March 2010, 2010-03-02; MS207.001.00209
    - African Union Panel for Sudan Technical Support Tasks and Staffing Plan, 2010-03-03; MS207.001.00210
  - Final report, 2013; MS207.001.00211
    - AUHIP FC report I - Final and Comprehensive Report, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00212
    - AUHIP FC report II -Darfur: Implementation of AUPD Recommendations, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00213
    - AUHIP FC report III - Democratization, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00214
    - AUHIP FC report IV - Completion of Outstanding Issues in the CPA, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00215
    - AUHIP FC report V - Post-Referendum and Post-Secession Issues, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00216
    - AUHIP FC report VI - Addressing the Conflict in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00217
    - AUHIP FC report VII - Abyei, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00218
    - AUHIP FC report VIII - Coordination of International Engagement, 2013-02-18; MS207.001.00219
  - Final signed documents, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.001.00220
    - Mekelle Memorandum of Understanding between the NCP and SPLM on Post-Referendum Issues and Arrangements, 2010-06-23; MS207.001.00221
      Agreement about the modalities and structures for future discussions on the post-referendum issues.
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Post-secession arrangements; National Congress Party; Sudan People's Liberation Movement
    - Post-2011 referendum arrangement negotiations financial, economic, and natural resources working group, 2010-12-23; MS207.001.00222
    - Political Parties Leadership Forum Meeting, 2011-02-17; MS207.001.00223
      Secession--South Sudan; Self-determination, national; Political parties; Interstate relations--Sudan
    - Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement on Temporary Arrangements for the Administration and Security of the Abyei Area, 2011-06-20; MS207.001.00224
      Abyei (Sudan); Sudan--Politics and government; Borderlands; Budget; Security; Internally displaced persons; Humanitarian Assistance; Sudan. Armed Forces; Sudan People's Liberation Movement; Abyei Joint Oversight Committee; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei Sudan People's Liberation Army; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei
    - Provisions on Border Issues, 2011-06-24; MS207.001.00225
    - Framework Agreement concerning Transitional Viability Arrangements, Oil and other Related Issues, 2011-06-25; MS207.001.00226
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Petroleum industry and trade; Oil fields; Petroleum pipelines--Fees; Sudan People's Liberation Movement
    - Draft Agreement of Cooperation Between the Government of the Sudan (GOS) and the Government of South Sudan (GOSS) Regarding Transbounary Water Resources, 2011-06-27; MS207.001.00227
    - Water Cluster, 2011-06-27; MS207.001.00228
    - Framework Agreement between the Government of Sudan and Sudan's People Liberation Movement North on Political Partnership between NCP and SPLMN, and Political and Security Arrangements in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan States, 2011-06-28; MS207.001.00229
      Nīl al Azraq (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Security; Political parties; Popular consultations; National Congress Party; Sudan People's Liberation Movement-North; Joint Political Committee (2011: Sudan)
    - Issues agreed concerning the petroleum sector and transitional viability arrangements, 2011-06-28; MS207.001.00230